Okay, let's move on to strategy. Our online promotion
好吧，让我们继续讨论策略。 我们的网上推广
Mobile social media from usage survey
从使用情况调查来看 移动社交媒体
People aged 20 to 30 years old
20岁至30岁人群
Instagram is social media. most used by people
Instagram 是社交媒体。 人们使用最多的
Among people in their 30s and 40s, the most popular platform is Cocoa Story.
在30多岁和40多岁的人群中， 最受欢迎的平台是Cocoa Story。
Followed by B Band and U Community.
其次是 B Band 和 U Community。
Instagram users are mostly male
Instagram 用户 大部分是男性
As for age
至于年龄
Most users are teenagers.
大多数用户是青少年。
"PR Joea"
“公关乔阿”
Are you tired after waiting for so long?
你等了这么久，累了吧？
What about your president?
那么你们的总统呢？
Coming soon.
很快就会到来。
They were the last to fight him.
他们是最后一批与他战斗的人。
You're used to this kind of thing.
你已经习惯了这种事情。
Who puts on an honest face to encourage me
谁摆出一副诚实的表情来鼓励我
Right here, my president.
就在这里，我的总统。
Yuncheng
云城
I don't need such encouragement.
我不需要这样的鼓励。
- Yun Qiao, are you ready? - Yes.
- 云乔，你准备好了吗？ - 是的。
OK, let's go.
好，我们走吧。
The last speaker is PR Joa.
最后一位演讲者是 PR Joa。
"Marketing Team Leader Gao Dongjun"
“营销一队组长 高东均”
a while.
一会儿。
Who will introduce it?
谁会来介绍呢？
Shouldn't the president be the one in attendance?
总统不应该是出席的人吗？
Yes, it’s not me, it’s Manager Park Yoon-joo...
是的，不是我， 是朴允珠经理……
Yes, the chairman is the host.
是的，主席就是主持人。
CEOs of other companies do the same.
其他公司的总裁也这样做。
Manager Park was the one who came up with this plan. So she will present it herself.
朴经理是提出这个计划的人。 所以她会亲自呈现。
The president himself said it.
总统亲自说过。
Everyone lets everyone else come up with plans.
每个人都让其他人提出计划。
Is it that difficult to understand?
有那么难理解吗？
Or are you not ready to present yet?
或者你还没有准备好展示？
Boss Song called Senior Jin?
宋老板打电话给金学长？
To attack her?
来攻击她？
So she's really here?
所以她真的来了？
Well, life is hard like that.
嗯，生活就是这样艰难。
Yes, then I will introduce it myself.
是的，那我就亲自介绍一下。
《Seyuu》
《世勇》
Not prepared. Also, there is a lack of sincerity.
没有做好准备。 另外，缺乏诚意。
what is it?
它是什么？
sorry.
对不起。
I didn't mean to hear it.
我不是有意要听的。
yes...
是...
If you choose not to wear makeup, I understand.
如果您选择不化妆，我理解。
in daily life
在日常生活中
But this is just cosmetic work.
但这只是装饰性的工作。
This is a press conference. new cosmetics
这是一场发布会。 新化妆品
You are the president of the company that has come to bid.
你是前来竞标的公司的总裁。
But still...
但仍然...
That is...
那是...
So, have you tried our products?
那么， 您尝试过我们的产品吗？
In this way, I will trust you. How can you do this job?
这样，我就会信任你。 你怎么能胜任这份工作呢？
Sorry, I have sensitive skin.
抱歉，我的皮肤很敏感。
I hope you can understand.
我希望你明白。
Haven't used it yet.
还没用过。
But this is really your problem.
但这确实是你的问题。
Damn it
该死
Am I asking for too much?
我的要求是不是太多了？
I think the expectation is to be professional. There's nothing wrong with acting professional.
我认为期望是专业的。 表现得专业一点也没有什么问题。
It's so uncomfortable.
太不舒服了。
Mr. Song, what's going on? You act like a brat.
宋总这是怎么了？ 你表现得像个小鬼。
This is a hot topic. Just got my Ph.D.
这是一个热门话题。刚刚获得博士学位。
Captain Song Sun Tae
宋善泰队长
I am Park Yoon Jo from PR Jo Ah.
我是 PR Jo Ah 的 Park Yoon Jo。
What I asked is outdated. is there anything you can do?
我问的东西已经过时了。你能做点什么吗？
Other company presidents: Do you also wear makeup?
其他公司总裁 你也化妆吗？
They're all men, right?
他们都是男人，对吧？
Oh, or because he's a man. So I don’t have to dress up.
哦，或者因为他是个男人。 所以我不用打扮。
If you are a true professional
如果你是真正的专业人士
You should wear makeup. Let's introduce cosmetic work.
你应该化妆。 让我们介绍一下化妆品工作。
Is this true regardless of whether you wear clothes or not ?
不管你平时穿不穿衣服， 都是这样吗？
May I have your name?
你叫什么名字？
Park Yoon Joo
朴允珠
Let’s take a closer look.
进一步介绍一下。
Yes, then let's get started.
是的，那么我们就开始吧。
"Happy dance"
“快乐的舞蹈”
“Shochu”
“烧酒”
By the way, does the President have sensitive skin?
顺便问一下，总统皮肤敏感吗？
nothing.
没什么。
I have had great skin since birth.
我从出生起就有很好的皮肤。
Compared to the body, it's just healthy skin.
与本体相比 这只是健康的皮肤。
"I wanted to ask something old-fashioned. Is there anything you can do?"
“我想问一些过时的事情。 你能做点什么吗？”
Yunjo is braver than I thought.
Yunjo比我想象的更勇敢。
It's not easy to do that under those circumstances .
在那种情况下做到这一点 并不容易。
I can not do anything.
我无能为力。
This has nothing to do with courage.
这与勇气无关。
I feel so bad.
我感觉如此糟糕。
At least she should give a speech. Gather experience
至少她应该做一个演讲。 收集经验
He said that the president of another company showed me this work in person.
他说另一家公司的总裁 我亲自展示了这个作品。
The president did the right thing.
总统做了正确的事。
In addition, I also practice regularly myself.
另外，我自己也经常练习。
It was a good experience.
这是一次很好的经历。
Their attitude is very bad.
他们的态度非常不好。
How many more decades have passed? Power-mad attitudes may never change.
又过去了多少个十年？ 权力狂的态度可能永远不会改变。
Because we are just supporting actors.
因为我们只是配角。
In fact we know and know
事实上我们知道并且知道
But you still have to do your best. In case they don't like us...
但你还是要尽力而为。 以免他们不喜欢我们...
Makes me sad.
让我伤心。
Oh my Yunqiao
哎哟我的云乔
Sorry, I'm late.
对不起，来晚了。
Mr. Earth Communications...
地球通讯先生...
Can I sit with you?
我可以和你坐在一起吗？
Yes
是的
I haven't seen my senior for a long time.
我已经很久没有见到我的前辈了。
I said I had to come over for a drink.
我说我得过来喝一杯。
- Yeah- So I asked if I could be in the band too.
- 是的 - 所以我问我是否也可以加入乐队。
Oh, yes, um...
哦，是的，嗯……
Come sit here.
过来坐这儿吧。
Ah right?
啊对？
Did you have dinner with your employees?
您与员工共进晚餐了吗？
Yes, I've eaten it.
是的，我已经吃过。
It's like they want to go drinking together.
就好像他们想一起去喝酒一样。
Oh, no wonder you call me when you have time.
哦，难怪你 有空的时候给我打电话。
Not because we miss each other.
不是因为我们想念彼此。
Come on, I'm thinking about it.
来吧，我正在考虑。
I would like to take care of you myself.
我愿意亲自照顾你。
I should make up for my mistakes.
我应该弥补我的错误。
That's not to say. You should bring your corporate card to use.
这并不是说。 您应携带公司卡使用。
Using your own card is another story.
使用自己的卡是另一回事。
I can assure you, this is my card.
我可以向你保证，这是我的卡。
But wait.
但等一下。
Why did you come to feed me? Pay for my shirt.
你为什么来喂我？ 付我的衬衫钱。
You should give me money.
你应该给我钱。
What? What's going on with you two?
什么？ 你们两个有什么事吗？
What shirt?
什么衬衫？
I had a chocolate latte disaster this morning.
今天早上我遭遇了巧克力拿铁灾难。
Oh, that's where you buy new shirts?
哦，那是你买新衬衫的地方？
You bought it with my credit card.
你用我的信用卡买的。
This is our company's business card.
这是我们公司的名片。
Then pay for the food.
然后支付食物费用。
Let's drink.
我们喝吧。
"'Celtics' Evaluation Form, Promotional Auction Presentation."
“‘凯尔特人队’评估表， 促销拍卖演示。”
"Celtics Online and Offline Campaign Plan PR Joa"
《凯尔特人队线上 线下竞选计划PR Joa》
You're used to this kind of thing.
你已经习惯了这种事情。
Put on an honest face and give me encouragement.
摆出诚实的表情并给我鼓励。
I do not need...
我不需要...
Such encouragement
那样的鼓励
"Call Yun Qiao."
“给云乔打电话。”
Unable to contact destination number.
无法联系目的地号码。
Please leave a message after the beep...
请在“嘟”声后留言...
Oh, you haven't come back yet?
哦，你还没回来吗？
I thought we all went back.
我以为我们都回去了。
Don't be too happy yet. I'm not going to have a drink.
还别高兴得太早。 我不打算喝一杯。
Why?
为什么？
The demo is now over.
演示现已结束。
So what, we ourselves are not present.
那又怎样，我们自己又没有呈现。
I went to see it.
我去看了。
This is a tiring process.
这是一个很累的过程。
Anyway, I can't go tonight.
无论如何，今晚我不能去。
Come on, why?
来吧，为什么？
- Can't go - Why?
- 不能去 - 为什么？
Why?
为什么？
- Stop - Why?
- 停下来 - 为什么？
Really, at that time , it made me want to cry.
真的，那个时候 这让我想哭。
that's right.
这是正确的。
- I really understand - Yeah
- 我真的明白 - 嗯
But it still hurts.
但还是很痛。
It's like they want to say "I got it, then go back."
就像他们想说的那样 “明白了，那就回去吧。”
- They look like this every time... - I know.
- 每次他们都是这个样子... - 我知道
I understand very well.
我非常明白。
The boss also wants to drink.
老板也想喝酒。
For example, "I want to go drinking with you again."
比如“我想再和你一起去喝酒”。
- Really? - Yes.
- 真的吗？ - 是的。
- If I get dumped, can I call my senior? - Yunjo, we are just supporting characters.
- 如果我被甩了，我可以给我的前辈打电话吗？ - Yunjo，我们只是配角。
- Congratulations on this auction .
- 这次拍卖 - 恭喜。
- He chose... - Thank you very much.
- 他选择了... - 非常感谢。
Earth Communications has
地球通讯已经
"Marketing Team Leader Go Dong-kyun"
“营销一队组长高东均”
Who will introduce it?
谁会来介绍呢？
Not prepared. Also, there is a lack of sincerity.
没有做好准备。 另外，缺乏诚意。
In this way, I will trust you. How can you do this job?
这样，我就会信任你。 你怎么能胜任这份工作呢？
- Senior must have really been drinking with me - He must be there
- 前辈一定是真的和我一起喝酒了 - 肯定就在那里
You know what?
你知道什么吗？
- When that happens, maybe we should meet. - Yes
- 当这种情况发生时，我们也许应该见面。 - 是的
The boss is lonely.
老板很孤独。
- Seniors, you must drink with me. - Why haven't you called me recently?
- 前辈们一定要陪我喝酒 - 你怎么最近没给我打电话？
- Ha - I'm very busy these days.
- 哈 - 这些天我很忙。
-Are you so busy that you don't have time to call me? - bring it on.
- 你这么忙没有时间给我打电话吗？ - 来吧。
- It's not like that... - The President
- 不像那样... - 总统
Yes
是的
President, do you really have no feelings?
总裁，你真的没有感觉吗？
That is,
那是，
I know.
我知道。
This is not EarthComm's fault.
这不是 EarthComm 的错。
Yuncheng
云城
but...
但...
I can't help but be jealous.
我忍不住嫉妒。
Why?
为什么？
Why do I hate it so much?
为什么我这么讨厌它？
I'm already drunk.
我已经醉了。
Yes, I'm drunk.
是的，我醉了。
Because then I will...
因为那样我就会...
excuse me
打扰一下
but the president
但总统
I know.
我知道。
Oh I see
原来是这样的
This circle...
这个圈子...
like this.
就像这样。
You are still the seniors and juniors. EarthComm President Who can be here?
你们还是前辈和后辈。 EarthComm 总裁谁能在场
- After everything I went through today - Yunjo
- 在我今天经历了这一切之后 - Yunjo
but...
但...
everything...
一切...
everything about it
关于它的一切
Is that a little too much?
是不是有点太过分了？
excuse me
打扰一下
What's wrong?
有什么不对？
Let's drink.
我们喝吧。
"Jiemin"
“杰民”
“Jaemin, you’ve received a new message.”
“渽民， 你收到一条新消息了。”
"Missed the call from Jae Min"
“未接在珉打来的电话”
"say something"
《说说话》
"Jiemin"
“杰民”
Answer the phone before I get angry. I was serious.
在我生气之前接电话吧。我是认真的。
Hey, I just sent you a message.
嘿，我刚刚给你发了一条消息。
how do you say?
你怎么说？
"Cloud Qiao Utopia"
《云 乔乌托邦》
What did you ask her to say?
你让她说什么？
"Answer the phone before I get mad. I'm telling the truth."
“在我生气之前接电话。 我在讲真话。”
She probably wants to meet here.
她大概想在这里见面。
It was like there was a war going on.
就好像发生了一场战争。
Then I'll go home first.
那我就先回家了。
this
这
Wherever you go, you call her personally.
无论你走到哪里，你都亲自给她打电话。
Listen, if you do something bad I confront her to end it all.
听着，如果你做了坏事 我面对她来结束这一切。
Stop putting it off, I understand.
别再拖延了，我明白。
I'm going in.
我要进去了。
You are richer than your boss.
你比你老板有钱。
Well, bring me the most expensive wine. It's in the store.
恩，拿最贵的酒来。 它在商店里。
Oh, okay, please wait a moment.
哦，好的，请稍等一下。
Hey, why are you walking around soaked?
喂，你怎么浑身湿透地走来走去？
I don't have an umbrella.
我没有伞。
You can purchase it here.
你可以在这里购买。
Walking in the rain like this, my head is going to be bald.
就这样走在雨中 这里的头要秃了。
not here
不在这里
This is where things get hollow.
这就是事情空洞的地方。
Another plot...
又是剧情...
- Let's have a drink first - Yeah
- 我们先喝一杯吧 - 嗯
again?
再次？
- This is Yoo Jae Min - said
- 这是柳在民 - 说
Yoo Jae-min
柳在民
Well, tell me.
嗯，说吧。
This is Yoo Jae Min.
这是柳在民。
This guy is really bad.
这家伙实在是太坏了。
Assistant Jiemin, please help me.
杰珉助理，请帮帮我。
Yes
是的
Congratulations.
恭喜。
Thank you so much
非常感谢
You belong there.
你属于那里。
- you know everything - well done
-你什么都知道 -干得好
- good job today - you seem used to this
-今天干得好 -你看起来对此很习惯
That's what makes me angry.
这就是让我生气的原因。
And the most angry
而最愤怒的
excuse me
打扰一下
Sorry, Yun Qiao.
对不起，云乔。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
This is understandable. Why couldn't he tell her first?
这是可以理解的。 为什么他不能先告诉她？
Is it right?
是对的吗？
I know.
我知道。
I just wanted to vent, that's all.
我只是想发泄一下，仅此而已。
Yes, let it out.
是的，放出来。
You can yell or cry all you want.
你可以随心所欲地喊叫或哭泣。
Stop it, you make me want to cry.
别说了， 你让我想哭。
But can I say one more thing?
但我还能再说一件事吗？
no matter what the result is
不管结果如何
I understand. How much do you plan to show?
我理解了 您打算展示多少？
It's really admirable.
实在是令人佩服。
Hehe, don’t you give people goosebumps when you say something like this? Am I the only one?
嘿嘿，你说这样的话不让人起鸡皮疙瘩吗？ 我是唯一一个？
In my heart, you are number one.
在我心里，你是第一。
Shut up you idiot.
闭嘴你个白痴。
hold hands and reconcile
牵手并和解
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
You can act like a child.
你可以表现得像个孩子。
like this?
像这样？
Then we made up.
然后我们就和好了。
correct?
正确的？
Ha ha.
哈哈。
Come, let's have a drink.
来，我们喝一杯吧。
collision
碰撞
OK
好的。
They say we get three chances in life.
他们说我们一生有三次机会。
Who said?
谁说？
I Ching
易经
what is it?
它是什么？
I really thought the opportunity was going to come
我真的以为 机会将会到来
But I was wrong.
但是我错了。
Really bad.
真的很糟糕。
But who will pay?
但谁来付钱呢？
- Hey you idiot - Hey you
- 嘿你这个白痴 - 嘿你
- Why? - You are the richest person in our group.
- 为什么？ - 你是我们组里最富有的人。
Didn't I tell you from the beginning , sir?
我不是一开始就告诉过你 ，先生吗？
Have you told me already?
你已经告诉我了吗？
- How much? - One million, eight hundred thousand won.
- 多少钱？ - 一百万、八十万韩元。
1.8 million won...
一百八十万韩元...
Hey, I'm a salaried employee.
嘿，我是一名受薪员工。
Your salary is more than mine.
你的工资比我多。
I'm also at a loss.
我也很茫然。
Why do I need to make money? I got so much too.
我为什么需要赚钱？ 我也得到了这么多。
- Are you joking? - honestly.
- 你在开玩笑吗？ - 说真的。
Strategic General Manager Lin Zhixian
战略总经理 林志贤
The only daughter of the founder of Serong. The late Lim Chang-soo
世容创始人的独生女。 已故的林昌洙
Affiliated to the Strategic Management Department
隶属于战略管理部
There is a strategic planning department.
有一个战略规划部门。
Human Resources Department
人力资源部
Legal Department
法律部
and our public relations department
和我们的公共关系部门
The truth is that the late Im Chang-soo
事实是已故的林昌洙
Create a strategic management department to give your daughter more power
创建战略管理部门 给女儿更多的力量
Because he is worried...
因为他担心……
She may not be able to take over the company. when he died
她可能无法接管公司。 当他去世的时候
"Vice President Zheng Jiuying of Shiyong Business Department "
“世勇事业部 郑久英副社长”
Yes, sir.
是的先生。
"Seyong, Sales Department, Kim Yeon-Soo, General Manager"
“销售部 Seyong， 总经理 Kim Yeon Soo”
Why?
为什么？
Because of Shi Yong’s driving force
因为世勇的推动力
This is the vice president of business. For example, is Zheng Jiuying still alive?
这是业务副总裁 比如郑九英还活着吗？
He is also the co-founder of Seyon. With the late Mr. Lim Chang-soo
他也是 Seyon 的联合创始人。 与已故的林昌洙先生
The relationship between Vice President and General Manager?
之间的关系 副总裁兼总经理？
OK
好的
Look outside.
看看外面。
《Seyuu》
《世勇》
But if you look inside a little bit…
但如果你稍微往里面看一下……
You will know.
你会知道的。
A fierce power struggle took place
发生了激烈的权力斗争
a while.
一会儿。
Assistant Jaemin, what do you think?
宰珉助理你说呢？
Where are you?
你在哪里？
Ha, are you in the conference room?
哈，你在会议室吗？
Ha, can't you see me?
哈，你看不见我吗？
Hey, here it is.
嘿，在这里。
what are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
What is the manager doing with the intern?
经理在和实习生做什么？
Summary of the situation in the Shi Yong government . Let them listen.
世勇政府情况概要 让他们听。
- Or historical drama introduction - Bingo
- 或历史剧介绍 - Bingo
Assistant Jaemin, what's wrong?
宰民助理有什么事吗？
Oh, Director Jon from the cosmetics department. I want to talk to you about the auction...
哦，化妆品部的乔恩局长。 我想和你谈谈拍卖的事...
Now Jaemin's assistant. You have a responsibility, don't you?
现在是渽民的助理 你有责任，不是吗？
take over from me
接替我
OK
好的
He's so cool.
他太酷了。
He's going to ask for help again, right?
他会再请求帮助一次，对吧？
I had no idea I was coming to the meeting today.
我不知道我今天要来参加会议。
Less than 49 days.
还不到49天。
This is not the Joseon era at all.
这根本不是朝鲜时代。
yes...
是...
It's not like you have to sit by the grave for 49 days.
这并不像你必须在坟墓旁边坐 49 天。
This is real.
这是真的。
I thought you wanted me to stay because I had something else to tell you.
我以为你要我留下来 因为我还有事要告诉你。
be patient.
要有耐心。
Be patient and let's work together.
要有耐心，让我们一起努力。
Thanks
谢谢
She probably doesn't know yet. Because there’s a lot to think about.
她大概还不知道。 因为有很多事情需要思考。
There's bad news.
有坏消息。
Just like the public relations aspect, it's not going to be very effective.
就像公共关系方面 效果不会很好。
I'm considering moving them. Affiliated to the business department
我正在考虑搬走他们。 隶属于业务部
I'll handle it myself.
我自己会处理的。
No
不
OK
好的
"General Manager of Strategy Department Lin Zhixian"
“战略部总经理 林志贤”
"Daguo Daily"
《大国日报》
"Bribery auction to replace Seyon's manufacturer?"
“贿赂拍卖会 更换Seyon的制造商？”
The person in charge of the public relations department was called.
叫来了公关部的负责人。
Yes
是的
"Planning Department"
“计划部门”
what is it?
它是什么？
We've been discussing this issue for some time.
我们已经讨论这个问题有一段时间了。
And the plan we chose...
而我们选择的计划...
That's the plan.
就是这个计划。
"Celtics Online and Offline Campaign Plan PR Joa"
《凯尔特人队线上 线下竞选计划PR Joa》
boss
老板
I know we should choose EarthComm.
我知道我们应该选择 EarthComm。
But Earth Communications You can use this plan instead.
但地球通讯 您可以改用此计划。
I've done this before.
我以前做过这个。
Since creative media strategy...
既然创意 媒体策略...
This is better.
这个比较好。
"Celtics Online and Offline Campaign Plan PR Joa"
《凯尔特人队线上 线下竞选计划PR Joa》
This really happened.
这真的发生了。
But the other company isn't Earth Communications.
但另一家公司 不是地球通讯。
But it used to be.
但以前确实如此。
What about regulations?
法规又如何呢？
There are no rules.
没有任何规定。
Who do you think the company didn't win the bid for this job?
你认为公司 谁没有赢得这份工作的投标
Are they going to say, "You don't have to pay us. Steal our ideas"?
他们会说：“你不必付钱给我们。 窃取我们的想法”？
They sell plans at a fair price, right?
他们出售计划 价格公道，对吗？
Let EarthComm take care of it.
让 EarthComm 来处理吧。
Whether to pay or not is their own business.
付不付钱是他们自己的事。
Anyway, let's proceed as planned. PR Joa.
不管怎样，还是按照计划进行吧。 公关乔阿。
Boss Song must be frightened.
宋老板肯定是吓坏了。
Gioia’s PR plan?
乔亚的公关计划？
I didn't expect this at all.
我根本没想到会这样。
No, say no.
不，说不。
Cosmetics Sales Team Leader A team, right?
化妆品销售组长 一个团队，对吗？
Yes
是的
Only a child would do such a thing.
只有孩子才会做这样的事。
Where are you from?
你来自哪里？
I think I'll use this plan. Can I throw it away?
我想我会使用这个计划。 我可以扔掉吗？
But PR Joa has a better plan...
但公关乔阿的计划更好......
damn it.
该死的。
Don't answer the phone during working hours?
上班时间不接电话？
Yoo Jae-min
柳在民
Will you go with him too?
你也跟他一起去吗？
gentlemen...
先生...
Yes, Manager Kim.
是的，金经理。
what is it?
它是什么？
Yes, I'm on my way.
是的，我正在路上。
Yes
是的
Come, follow me.
来，跟我来。
"General Manager of Strategy Department"
《战略部总经理》
In summary...
综上所述...
You take the money and throw it over your head. And let it come back to haunt us?
你接过钱，把它扔到头上。 并让它再次困扰我们吗？
It is not.
它不是。
They will be releasing new information soon. Come fix the news and...
很快他们就会发布新消息。 快来修复新闻并...
No one watches the news.
没有人看新闻。
read.
阅读。
The Vice President will definitely read it.
副总统肯定会读的。
Is there nothing?
难道什么都没有吗？
Let's break the big news about the good things Seyong is doing.
让我们发布 有关 Seyong 所做的好事的重大新闻。
Our media-loving Vice President would be delighted.
我们热爱媒体的副总统会很高兴的。
- Boss Song - Yes.
- 宋老板 - 是的。
What's wrong with this?
这有什么问题吗？
what is it?
它是什么？
I'll try to think about it.
我会尝试考虑一下。
Who are you?
你是谁？
Assistant Manager Liu Jae-min from Public Relations Team 2
助理经理 柳在民 来自公关二组
Yoo Jae-min
柳在民
Someone who writes a good manifesto?
写出好的宣言的人？
I'm surprised you remember this.
我很惊讶你还记得这一点。
The general manager is really smart.
总经理真是聪明人。
What about Ryu's assistant?
那么Ryu的助理呢？
Can you come up with great ideas quickly?
你能快速想出好主意吗？
drowning in news about our abuse of power
淹没 我们滥用权力的新闻
What other companies do we don’t do.
其他公司做什么 但我们没有这么做。
But we shouldn't imitate them.
但我们不应该模仿他们。
What makes us look good and different?
是什么让我们看起来又好看又与众不同？
Employment without discrimination
就业无歧视
Non-discriminatory employment?
非歧视就业？
I hear this sound every day.
每天都会听到这样的声音。
Are you saying there is discrimination?
你说有歧视吗？
This is something every company does. Except us.
这是每个公司都会做的事情。 除了我们。
Regarding hiring only experienced people I think giving employees...
关于只雇用有经验的人 我认为给员工...
Choose the people you want to work with. It's not like the others.
选择你想一起工作的人。 它不像其他人。
OK
好的
be prepared
做好准备
- Next executive meeting - Yes.
- 下次执行会议 - 是的。
Then send out a press release and let the media be everywhere except the "Da Guo Daily".
然后发出新闻稿 让媒体无处不在 除了《大国日报》。
But General Manager , if we do this, the consequences...
但总经理 如果我们这样做 后果...
Then withdraw the ad.
然后撤回广告。
Don't let it trample you. Take action first.
不要让它践踏你。 先采取行动。
you can go now.
你可以走了。
-I can go. -Yes.
-我可以走了 -是的
This is the latest news from Mr. Goo Eui-jung.
这是具义正先生的最新消息。
Many Korean companies invited her to participate in this event.
多家韩国企业 邀请她参加这次活动。
But she refused.
但她都拒绝了。
She's your college friend. She might accept...
她是你的大学朋友。她可能会接受...
We hate each other.
我们互相憎恨。
There is a big debate about a man.
关于一个男人，有一个很大的争论。
I haven't spoken to her in over 20 years.
我已经有20多年没有和她说过话了。
"2022 Influential Female Leaders Public Relations Consultant Goo Eui-jung"
《2022年影响力女性领袖 公关顾问具宜贞》
"manage"
“管理”
“Jenny Gu’s American Dream is real.”
“顾珍妮的美国梦 这是真的。”
- Mr. President - Yeah.
- 总统先生 - 嗯。
chirchan's children
奇尔陈的孩子们
- Here we come - Are you hungry?
- 我们来了 - 你饿吗？
so cute.
太可爱了。
She died, just like her mother.
她死了，就像她母亲一样。
- Very similar - Yes
- 非常相似 - 是的
Look at those chubby cheeks.
看看那些胖乎乎的脸颊。
- So cute. - Oh my god, so beautiful.
- 太可爱了 - 天哪，太漂亮了
but...
但...
From now on, Li Zhezhang's life will be difficult.
从现在开始，李哲张的日子会不好过。
Raising a child alone is difficult these days. Just twins
如今，独自抚养孩子很困难。 不过是双胞胎
That's it.
就是这样。
And, with no one to help her, the work was really hard.
而且，没有人帮助她， 工作真的很辛苦。
I need to make a lot of money.
我需要赚很多钱。
It's easy to say.
这很容易说。
This is real.
这是真的。
I have more responsibility to take care of myself.
我有更多的责任来照顾自己。
Damn it
该死
- You had a drink. - Have a good meal.
- 你喝了一杯。 - 好好吃饭吧。
- Thank you, good bye.
- 谢谢你 再见。
welcome.
欢迎。
- Hello - I will definitely wait.
- 你好 - 我肯定会等。
Is this your favorite bakery?
这是你最喜欢的面包店吗？
Check it out, it's very popular.
看看吧，很受欢迎。
The bread wasn't very tasty , but it was very popular.
面包不是很好吃 ，但是很受欢迎。
How did I get interested?
我是怎么感兴趣的？
- Buy it and take it home? - but...
- 买它带回家吧？ - 但是...
I need to find something to seduce them.
我需要找到一些东西来引诱他们。
she thinks...
她想...
Do they have the money to promote the store?
他们有钱来推广商店吗？
Well, if the idea is good and not much money...
好吧，如果这个主意好的话 钱不多...
- Mr. President - Yeah.
- 总统先生 - 嗯。
I will be looking for new clients this time.
这次我会寻找新客户。
Oh, did you get a sales job?
哦，你找到销售工作了吗？
So thank you very much.
那么非常感谢你。
But I'm still ashamed
但我还是很羞愧
Don't be shy.
别害羞。
I'll take another look here. Please feel free to come.
我会再看看这里。 请随意前来。
Yes, I'll throw it away for you.
是的，我会帮你扔​​掉它。
Work hard to find new customers.
努力寻找新客户。
Please, I'm so confused.
求求你了，我好迷茫。
But I like it.
但我喜欢它。
excuse me
打扰一下
I wonder why it's so loud?
我想知道为什么这么大声？
This is protein bread.
这是蛋白质面包。
I know, but it's not the only one. This is where I make my protein bread.
我知道，但这不是唯一的。 这是我做蛋白质面包的地方。
They only sell limited quantities.
他们只出售有限的数量。
And it tastes better. There are other types of protein bread
而且更好吃。 还有其他类型的蛋白质面包
Here, let us gather together.
在这里，让我们欢聚一堂。
- Okay - Hey, shut up.
- 好吧 - 嘿，闭嘴。
- Where are you? - OK.
- 你在哪里？ - 好的。
Hey, watch my back, protect me.
嘿，看着我的背，保护我。
Ok, I see.
好的，我明白了。
this
这
Wait here.
在这儿等着。
damn it!
该死的！
Hey, I told you to watch your back.
嘿，我告诉过你要小心你的背后。
Why...
为什么...
- I can't shoot. - Are you kidding me? Hold.
- 我不会开枪 - 你在开玩笑吗？操。
Eun-soo, what are you doing?
恩秀，你在做什么？
- You have no sense of direction - Where to go?
- 你没有方向感 - 去哪儿？
Here, load the bullets.
在这里，装载子弹。
- Hey , what are you doing?
- 嘿 ，你在做什么？
- Hey, take it. - Damn, take it.
- 嘿，拿着吧 - 妈的，拿去吧。
- Yes - That's great.
- 是的 - 太棒了。
- Great - What, why are you here?
- 太好了 - 什么，你为什么来这里？
It's been a while.
有一阵子了。
WHO？
WHO？
Haizu's sister.
海祖的姐姐。
nice to meet
很高兴认识
Hey, why did you say my sister is dead?
哎，你为什么说我妹妹死了？
Is it right?
是对的吗？
When will I die?
我什么时候会死？
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
continue.
继续。
Is it a good idea to join the army after graduation?
毕业后参军好不好？
I found the right way here.
我在这里找到了正确的方法。
No
不
I heard that high school students like it very much.
听说高中生很喜欢。
Especially a woman like her.
尤其是像她这样的女性。
what is it?
它是什么？
protein bread
蛋白质面包
Yes, like a kid in school. We will eat a lot.
是的，就像一个在学校的孩子。 我们会吃很多。
I saw that it can help you lose weight.
我看到说可以减肥。
Do high school students lose a lot of weight?
高中生体重下降很多吗？
you're old.
你老了。
- Hey, protein bread - cool, awesome.
- 嘿，蛋白质面包 - 酷，棒极了。
- Come, have a good meal - Yeah
- 来，好好吃饭 - 嗯
- Awesome. Thank you. - Very delicious.
- 太棒了 谢谢 - 非常好吃
this is delicious.
这个好吃。
- Awesome - Delicious
- 太棒了 - 好吃
Can it help you lose weight?
它能帮助你减肥吗？
- It's really delicious. - It's delicious.
- 真的很好吃 - 很好吃
Is it tasty?
好吃吗？
very soft
很软
- Is this protein bread? - delicious.
- 这是蛋白质面包吗？ - 很好吃。
- Yes - try it.
- 是的 - 尝试一下。
- Very delicious
- 非常好吃
Manager Jin I just had a chat with Manager Jin.
金经理 刚刚和金经理聊了聊。
General Manager Kim Yeon- soo From the sales department?
金延洙总经理 来自销售部门？
We must follow the plan. PR Joa
我们必须遵循计划。 公关若阿
Call EarthComm's Seo Dong Hoon and tell him to proceed as planned.
致电 EarthComm 的 Seo Dong Hoon 然后告诉他按照计划进行。
That Jon Da Jeong girl, I...
那个 Jon Da Jeong 女孩，我...
Then come on, say you understand me.
那就来吧，说你理解我。
I don’t want to believe I’m putting it off. The general manager is also involved.
我不想相信我在拖延它。 总经理也参与其中。
Listen, tell him to start making new plans.
听着，告诉他开始制定新计划。
It looks like it was their idea.
看起来这是他们的主意。
What
什么
Nothing.
什么也没有。
"Celtics Online and Offline Campaign Plan PR Joa"
《凯尔特人队线上 线下竞选计划PR Joa》
Yes, I understand.
是的我明白。
what are you planning to do?
你打算做什么？
sorry.
对不起。
I'm not laughing at you.
我不是在笑你。
hair...
头发...
I'll handle it myself.
我自己会处理的。
《Seyuu》
《世勇》
"Angus Bread"
《安格斯面包》
You two were just baking. And running a store leaves little time.
你们两个刚刚在烘烤。 而经营商店几乎没有时间。
We will take care of your social media accounts.
我们将照顾您的社交媒体帐户。
We're going to build absolutely an online store.
我们将建造 绝对是网上商店。
You may be popular among teenagers
你可能很受欢迎 在青少年中
You have to take this seriously.
你必须认真对待这件事。
Now this market...
现在这个市场...
At the moment we don't have enough money to promote it.
目前我们没有足够的资金来推广它。
We will discuss payment terms later. Is it good after sales increase?
稍后我们再讨论付款条件。 销量增加后好不好？
very good.
很好。
Yes
是的
here it is.
这里是。
If you try it...
如果你尝试一下...
"Angus Bread"
《安格斯面包》
“Angus bread #protein bar #protein cake”
“安格斯面包 #蛋白质棒#蛋白质蛋糕”
"Blind Test Wheel"
“盲测轮”
"Chairman Xu Dongxun, evaluate based on ability."
“徐东勋会长， 根据能力来评价。”
"Celtics Online and Offline Campaign Plan PR Joa"
《凯尔特人队线上 线下竞选计划PR Joa》
"Angus Bread"
《安格斯面包》
Hello everyone
大家好
It's Hai Qiao.
是海乔。
This is a bakery called Angs Bread. I will review their products...
这是一家名为Angs Bread的面包店。 我会审查他们的产品...
Okay, here...
好吧，这边...
-Hello boss. ​​-Hello.
-你好，老板。 ​​-你好。
Hello
你好
I just saw something super cute.
我刚刚看到了一些超级可爱的东西。
so cute.
太可爱了。
I'm finally going to try their bread, let's go.
我终于要尝尝他们的面包了， 走吧。
This is protein bread.
这是蛋白质面包。
Even if you eat it, you won't gain weight.
即使吃，也不会发胖。
Mae Haek is delicious.
Mae Haek 非常美味。
What's this? Very tasty.
这是什么？非常好吃。
"Have you ever tried Angus bread? The protein bread is delicious."
“你吃过安格斯面包吗？ 蛋白质面包很好吃。”
- It's really good. - Very delicious.
- 真的很棒 - 很好吃
- But Tan - So cute.
- 但是谭 - 太可爱了。
So cute, so cute, the logo is adorable.
太可爱了，太可爱了，标志很可爱。
This is a donut that won't make you fat.
这是一个不会让你发胖的甜甜圈。
“#honestreview#donutreview#taste”
“#诚实的评论#甜甜圈评论#taste”
Normally I don't eat bread. But I like this.
平时我不吃面包。 但我喜欢这个。
This is protein bread. Eat without feeling guilty.
这是蛋白质面包。 吃东西，不要感到内疚。
"Nosab, it's a nice day today. Come talk to us."
“诺萨布，今天天气很好。 来和我们谈谈吧。”
"Ang Bread, have you heard of it? It's so popular, go and buy it."
“昂面包，你听过吗？ 这么受欢迎，你去买吧。”
“Eat protein bread when you’re tired.”
“累了就吃蛋白质面包。”
The chocolate flavor is very rich.
巧克力的味道非常浓郁。
Is it delicious?
好吃吧？
"Hai Zuyu, have you ever eaten this?"
“海祖浴， 你吃过这个吗？”
Have you eaten?
你吃过吗？
"Angus Bread"
《安格斯面包》
"Here's the snack you asked for."
“这是你要的点心。”
"You have to carry it with you forever."
“你必须永远带着它。”
“The bread in this store is delicious.”
“这家店的面包很好吃。”
"Order payment date"
“订单付款日期”
"President"
“主席”
president
总统
Um?
嗯？
Come quickly.
快点过来吧。
Damn, what?
该死的，什么？
How is this going?
这是怎么回事？
look at this.
看这个。
"Order, payment, refund, cancellation, return"
“订单、付款、退款、 取消、退货”
"Net balance in the last 7 days: 23,493,500 won"
“最近7天的净余额： 23,493,500韩元”
crazy
疯狂的
Sales surged.
销量猛增。
Unbelievable, right?
难以置信，对吧？
Yes, it is rising.
是的，它正在上涨。
This is Yun Qiao.
这是云乔。
I did it.
我做到了。
It's all over.
都结束了。
Oh my lucky star mom is so talented.
哦，我的幸运星妈妈真是太有才华了。
Wow, awesome.
哇，太棒了。
"Daguo Daily"
《大国日报》
"If you can't stop eating bread, then treat yourself to it. 'Protein Bread'"
“如果你无法停止吃面包， 然后给自己吃。‘蛋白质面包’”
"'Protein bread' is made with protein powder..."
“‘蛋白面包’是用蛋白粉做的……”
"Daeguk Daily Reporter Choi Hye-young"
《大国日报记者崔惠英》
station...
车站...
Hey, you workaholic.
嘿，你这个工作狂。
Are you OK? Are you happy and excited?
你好吗？你高兴、兴奋吗？
you do not know. I'm in heaven.
你不知道。 我在天堂。
"Daodong Paradise"
《道东天堂》
- Ha - Starry Sky Paradise...
- 哈 - 星空天堂...
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Anyway, thanks for the message.
不管怎样，谢谢你的消息。
When did you give it to Reporter Choi?
你什么时候给崔记者的？
I'm pretty good at it, right?
我很擅长，对吧？
She couldn't have asked for a better friend.
她找不到更好的朋友了。
She is addicted to me.
她对我上瘾了。
Her income is much less than mine.
她的收入比我少很多。
But you still owe me.
但你还是欠我的。
Why does it sound like this?
为什么听起来像这样？
Don't change the subject.
不要转移话题。
So disgusting
真恶心
"Yun Qiao"
“云乔”
Yes, said Yoo Jae-min.
是的，柳在民说。
"Recruiting experienced staff"
“招聘有经验的员工”
“Sifting through closed data by lower-level employees”
“通过封闭式数据筛选 由下层员工”
"No qualifications specified . No personal relationships were exploited."
“未指定资格 没有利用任何私人关系。”
"Employees choose their colleagues..."
“员工会选择自己的同事……”
When posting, emphasize the word "grassroots employees"
发帖时强调这个词 “基层员工”
And emphasize "only use experience"
并强调 “只用经验”
Yes
是的
This is indeed the case and must be clearly stated. This is a temporary position
确实如此，必须明确说明。 这是一个临时职位
I thought this was a permanent position.
我以为这是一个永久职位。
If it was so easy to get a permanent position, why open applications?
如果获得固定职位有那么容易的话 为什么要开放申请？
if they do a good job
如果他们做得好的话
In two years, I might be hired.
两年后，我也许就能被录用。
It's so hard to prove yourself in Seiyong .
在 Seiyong 证明自己 就是这么难。
Why
为什么
I’m afraid people won’t apply. Because it's a temporary position?
恐怕人家不会申请。 因为是临时职位？
No, people must be swarming like bees.
不， 人们一定像蜜蜂一样蜂拥而至。
Korea is simply hell on earth.
韩国简直就是人间地狱。
Yes, that's what I'm saying.
是的，这就是我要说的。
You can leave now.
你现在可以离开了。
Jia Min is probably the only one. Within our PR team, our second team
贾珉恐怕是唯一一个吧。 在我们的公关团队中，我们的第二团队
who actually works here
谁真正来这里工作
real
真的
There is another me.
还有另一个我。
See you tomorrow.
明天见。
are you happy?
你快乐吗？
Are you happy that you are good at spending time alone?
你对自己善于独处感到高兴吗？
Well, this is the team’s ace in the hole.
嗯，这是球队的王牌。
Believe it.
相信它。
"No qualifications specified. Just experience required."
“未指定资格 只需使用经验即可。”
"Lower-level staff, will you filter and close this information?"
“基层员工 你会过滤并关闭这些信息吗？”
"They are accepting applications. In terms of work ability"
“他们正在接受申请。 从工作能力来说”
"Do not view data, do not specify attributes"
“不查看数据，不指定属性”
"I applied for this round, but no information was disclosed. Let's go to Xie Yong's house."
“去申请了这一轮，但没有透露任何信息。 我们去谢勇家吧。”
"Recruitment of experienced employees 2022 special round"
“招聘有经验的员工 2022年特别轮”
“No qualifications specified, only work experience.”
“未指定资格 只看工作经验。”
"feature"
“特征”
"Workspace"
“工作空间”
"Education, language proficiency, gender, age: not specified"
“教育程度、语言能力、 性别、年龄：未指定”
The bus is coming.
公共汽车来了。
"Jaemin received new news."
“渽民 收到新消息了。”
"Shiyong Official Website"
《世勇官方网站》
excuse me
打扰一下
"Recruitment of experienced employees 2022 special round"
“招聘有经验的员工 2022年特别轮”
“No qualifications specified, only work experience.”
“未指定资格 只看工作经验。”
- Thank you - Yeah
- 谢谢 - 嗯
Thanks
谢谢
Yes, bye.
是的，再见。
is it here?
是这里吗？
Yes, Building 103.
是的，103号楼。
Building 103, yes.
103号楼，没错。
- is that so? - Come on, let's go.
- 是这样吗？ - 快点，我们走吧。
- Oh my God
- 哦天哪 - 哦天哪 花甲
- No, I'm dead. - Be careful.
- 不，我死了 - 小心点
Oh, it's going to hurt.
噢，会痛的。
deadly
死的
excuse me
打扰一下
- It's okay - Ms. Huajia
- 没关系 - 华佳女士
feels good.
感觉很好。
Oh, Mr. Yunqiao.
哦，云乔先生。
-This is my mom -ha
-这是我妈妈 -哈
I will take you there myself. You go.
我亲自带你去，你走吧。
Bro, I'm sorry.
兄弟，对不起。
Wait, Hua...
等等，华...
deadly
死的
Damn it
该死
Where can I find such a man?
这样的男人哪里找？
I still have stuff, right?
我还有东西，对吗？
Go bake with those people. To prove it?
和那些人一起去烤吧。 为了证明这一点？
I still have stuff.
我还有东西。
Miss Huajia
华佳小姐
As for you, no.
至于你，则没有。
Hey, why have you never dated anyone else?
嘿，你为什么从来没有和别人约会过？
real
真的
How would you feel if your daughter went to Seyong to work ?
如果你女儿去塞勇打工 你会感觉如何？
You don't like men?
你不喜欢男人？
Women, if you like women, go find them.
女人，如果你喜欢女人，就去找她们。
I ask you how you feel. If I go to work in Seyong
我问你感觉如何。 如果我去Seyong工作
So are you bored?
所以你很无聊吗？
Hello
你好
Wow!
哇！
Look for
寻找
how do you say?
你怎么说？
What do you think I should do?
你觉得我应该怎么做？
Should I say no and no longer work with Se Yong?
我应该拒绝 并不再与Se Yong合作吗？
damn it.
该死的。
There is a refrigerator outside.
外面有一个冰箱。
There's soju in it.
里面有烧酒。
- Go get it. - Senior
- 去拿它。 - 前辈
So what do you want to do?
那么你想做什么？
So please tell me what I should do.
所以请告诉我我应该做什么。
Then I'll do it.
那我就去做。
I don't know anything else.
我不知道其他事情。
Yes
是的
Take Manager Park as an example.
以朴经理为例。
These are all Yun Qiao's masterpiece.
这都是云乔的杰作。
What is most important to the company?
对公司来说最重要的是什么？
sustainable development
可持续发展
So what makes a company sustainable?
那么是什么让一家公司可持续发展呢？
First, a company must have a market.
首先，一个公司必须有市场。
Selling products and services
销售产品和服务
Secondly, we must know what is the financial status of the company?
其次，我们必须知道 公司的财务状况如何？
Will make business decisions that are always correct
将做出商业决策 总是正确的
last but not least
最后但并非最不重要
The world must still exist.
世界一定还存在。
This is the reason for "SPP".
这就是“S.P.P”的原因。
It stands for environment, society and governance.
它代表环境、社会 和治理。
This is important nowadays.
如今这很重要。
Because of this, we must pay attention to...
正因为如此，我们必须要注意...
All factors This has a greater impact on SPP.
所有因素 这对 S.P.P. 影响更大。
Make our business sustainable
让我们的业务可持续发展
not just for ourselves
不只是为了我们自己
but...
但...
for the future of this world
为了这个世界的未来
and our descendants
和我们的子孙
Thanks
谢谢
Miss
女士
"New York"
“纽约”
You don't have to call the lady. When the two of us are together it's okay.
你不用打电话给小姐。 当我们两个人在一起的时候就没事了。
They sent me because I knew we were good friends.
他们派我来 因为我知道我们是好朋友。
Linda
琳达
Thank you for your suggestion, but...
谢谢你的提议，但是...
Is there a "but"?
有“但是”吗？
I don't want to hear it anymore.
我不想再听了。
I stopped playing politics for a while.
我有一段时间不再玩政治了。
There's no big reason for this.
这没什么太大的理由。
People still want Jenny.
人们仍然想要珍妮。
I failed too.
我也失败了。
And it was successful too.
而且它也很成功。
are you sure?
你确定吗？
Yes
是的
OK
好的
I can't be convinced if Jenny is sure.
如果珍妮确定的话 我无法被说服。
Now working as a consultant How are you?
现在担任顾问 你好吗？
Excellent...
出色地...
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Jenny
珍妮
Why don't you take a break?
你为什么不休息一下呢？
You look very tired.
你看起来很累。
you know me.
你了解我。
This is enough to charge your energy up to 100%.
这足以将你的能量充至 100%。
My mission must have failed.
我的任务肯定失败了。
Hey Jenny.
嘿珍妮。
The coffee is delicious.
咖啡很好吃。
What brand is it?
它是什么品牌？
I think I told your secretary not to come.
我想我已经告诉你的秘书 不要来了。
I don't see any messages being received.
我没有看到收到任何消息。
Got it, but didn't pay much attention to it.
收到了，但没有多加注意。
- So - it hasn't changed at all.
- 所以 - 它根本没有改变。
Do what you want as usual.
像往常一样做你想做的事。
That's my charm.
这就是我的魅力。
I want you to help me.
我想要你帮助我。
I?
我？
Why should I help?
我为什么要帮忙？
China Association for Science and Technology
中科协
If you accept this job I will give you everything you want
如果你接受这份工作 我会给你你想要的一切
If you think I'd take a job for the money...
如果你认为我会为了钱接受一份工作...
Can you make me kneel down?
你能让我跪下吗？
I need you more than anyone right now.
现在我比任何人都更需要你。
"Utopia"
“乌托邦”
I don’t know if Yin Zu applied. Didn't get any news at all.
不知道尹祖有没有申请。 根本没有得到任何消息。
She probably won't tell. Is it because I'm afraid of being embarrassed?
她大概不会告诉。 是因为我怕丢脸吗？
this is possible.
这是可能的。
But I bet she applied for 10,000 won.
但我打赌她申请了10,000韩元。
Me too. I bet she applied for 20,000 won.
我也是。 我打赌她申请了两万韩元。
Are you kidding me? You have to stab the other person.
你在开玩笑吧？ 你必须刺伤对方。
you are still working?
你还在工作？
Actually I said
其实我说了
They will announce it soon.
他们很快就会宣布。
I will know if it is announced.
如果宣布的话，我会知道的。
"inbox"
“收件箱”
"Forward: List of applicants who have passed the selection process"
“转发：申请人名单 已通过选拔程序的人”
What?
什么？
Yeah? You participated too, right?
是吗？你也参加了，对吧？
Tell me, Yoo Jae-min.
告诉我吧，柳在民。
Hey, wait a minute.
嘿，等一下。
"Forward: List of applicants who have passed the selection process"
“转发：申请人名单 已通过选拔程序的人”
knock knock
敲敲
Chairman Xu Dongxun
徐东勋会长
a while.
一会儿。
The president left work early today.
今天总统提前下班了。
Today I come to see Mr. Park Yoon-jo.
今天我来见朴润祖先生。
I? What's wrong?
我？怎么了？
Do you want to go to dinner together?
你想一起去吃饭吗？
Why...
为什么...
First, I have a suggestion for you.
首先，我有一个建议给你。
Have you seen the protein bread sale?
您看到蛋白质面包的促销了吗？
I do it by myself
我自己做的
Now he is well-known in the public relations world.
现在在公关界小有名气。
Everyone wants to know who I am.
每个人都想知道我是谁。
This says too much.
这说得太多了。
It got a little bit of attention. In the world of digital PR
它得到了一点点关注。 在数字公关世界中
this is not me.
这不是我。
Promoting protein bread is me.
推广蛋白质面包就是我。
Yes, I can accept that.
是的，我可以接受。
Are you here to tease me?
你是来逗我的吗？
No.
不。
So let's go have a drink?
那么我们去喝一杯吧？
From what I understand, your neck is stiff.
据我所知，你的脖子僵硬了。
Can I ask what the offer is?
我可以问一下优惠是什么吗？
Is this here?
这是这里吗？
Do you want me to stand up and talk?
你想让我站起来说话吗？
"Forward: List of applicants who have passed the selection process"
“转发：申请人名单 已通过选拔程序的人”
"Some candidates have been selected. Three people in total..."
“有些候选人被选中了。 一共三个人……”
OK
好的
I'm here to invite you to work.
我是来邀请你来上班的。
Serve as a leader on one of the EarthComm teams .
担任EarthComm团队 之一的领导者。
" Park Yoon-joo, Strategic Management Department and Public Relations Department"
《战略管理部 公关部朴允珠”
"The characters, events, organizations, and backgrounds in the play are all fictitious."
“剧中的人物、事件、组织、背景都是虚构的。”
Narrated by Thicha Leelawongpanich
Thicha Leelawongpanich 旁白